Ankit Kumar Sharma

Full - Stack developer using PHP and Magento with over 3 years of professional experience in all phases of Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), focusing on web-based client-server (multi-tier architecture) applications, mobile, and database development.

07, Ramnagar, Kathumar, Alwar (Raj.) 321607

+91 6375855078

ankit2000sharma.jcb@gmail.com Skype: live:89e64692b08c6b93

EXPERIENCE

IFlair Web Technologies Pvt. Ltd, Ahmedabad (Magento Developer)

Jul 2022 - PRESENT

- Magento version upgrade
- Security patches upgrade
- Maintaining Multi-Vendor website
- Worked well with the team and independently.
- Magento Maintenance and management executive.
- Magento Upgrade And Basics of Cross Migration

Ascure Technologies, Jaipur (Magento Developer)

Jan 2021 - Jul 2022

- Gathered and defined customer requirements to develop clear specifications for projects
- Planned, Developed, Tested, Deployed, and maintained websites
- Client management: Maintained client satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing client needs and resolving concerns.

Road Ahead Technology, Jaipur (Aws Cloud Practitioner)

Jun 2020 - Jan 2021

PROJECTS

Ardellshop.com

- Setup the 17 Stores in single magneto Setup
- Advance Js bundling on 17store

Masongarments.com

- Upgrade Magento 2.3.4 to Magento 2.4.5-p1
- Upgrade theme with all the modules
- Resolved conflict after upgrade

Onlyprime

- End-to-end solution multivendor websites like a marketplace
- Create the main and child product with the CSV and after deleting save the original product data.

EDUCATION

B. Tech(CSE), Jaipur— 2021 Aug-2017 - Apr-2021 Parentage: 61%

SKILLS

- 1. PHP
- 2. Magento
- 3. JavaScript
- 4. HTML, CSS, jQuery
- 5. Knockout Js
- 6. Linux, AWS, GitHub

LANGUAGES

Hindi, English